[
  {
    "question": "Who was elected person of the year 2023?",
    "answer": "Taylor Swift",
    "tags": "general knowledge",
    "date": "2024-01-19"
  },
  {
    "question": "Today, January 19th, is the anniversary of the birth of the scottish inventor, widely regarded as the father of the modern steam engine. What's his name?",
    "answer": "James Watt",
    "tags": "general knowledge",
    "date": "2024-01-19"
  },
  {
    "question": "In a QWERTY keyboard, which letter sits on the right of the letter Y?",
    "answer": "U",
    "tags": "general knowledge",
    "date": "2024-01-19"
  },
  {
    "question": "Situated in the south pacific, the so called point Nemo is famous for being the point the denotes what?",
    "answer": "Maximum distance from every single livable area",
    "tags": "general knowledge",
    "date": "2024-01-19"
  },
  {
    "question": "Epstein has allegedly forbidden the participation to an orgy to whom?",
    "answer": "Stephen Hawking",
    "tags": "general knowledge",
    "date": "2024-01-19"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which region, shared by Argentina and Chile, is famous for being the souther human walkable area on Earth?",
    "answer": "Patagonia",
    "tags": "general knowledge",
    "date": "2024-01-19"
  },
  {
    "question": "Apple was for few seconds not the most valuable company in the world on Thursday 11th after more than 18 months. Which company was?",
    "answer": "Microsoft",
    "tags": "general knowledge",
    "date": "2024-01-19"
  },
  {
    "question": "Bridges in the Euro banknotes don't exist. Only one of them was built after the release of the banknotes with the idea of actually building the bridge. Where is it?",
    "answer": "Rotterdam, Netherlands",
    "tags": "general knowledge",
    "date": "2024-01-19"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many chords are there in a standard orchestra violin?",
    "answer": "4",
    "tags": "general knowledge",
    "date": "2024-01-19"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is currently staying in the graveyard spot just next to Marylin Monroe?",
    "answer": "Hugh Heffner",
    "tags": "general knowledge",
    "date": "2024-01-19"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which actor or actress is currently holding the record for staying the most time in free diving without breathing?",
    "answer": "Kate Winslet, previously Tom Cruise",
    "tags": "general knowledge",
    "date": "2024-01-19"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is the nationality of Ernesto Guevara, also called \"el Che\"?",
    "answer": "Rosario, Argentina",
    "tags": "general knowledge",
    "date": "2024-01-19"
  },
  {
    "question": "In which city can you find the famous Bourbon Street?",
    "answer": "New Orleans",
    "tags": "general knowledge",
    "date": "2024-01-19"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many leap years did we have in the XX century?",
    "answer": "24",
    "tags": "general knowledge",
    "date": "2024-01-19"
  },
  {
    "question": "We recently held the 10th anniversary of one of the biggest naval disasters just right between Tuscany and Corsica. What was the name of the Cruise?",
    "answer": "Titanic",
    "tags": "general knowledge",
    "date": "2024-01-19"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which English word denoting good luck in making unexpected discoveries takes his name from the old name of Sri Lanka?",
    "answer": "Serendipity",
    "tags": "general knowledge",
    "date": "2024-01-19"
  },
  {
    "question": "If, from the city of Los Angeles, I start moving westwise, which is the first country that I find?",
    "answer": "Japan",
    "tags": "general knowledge",
    "date": "2024-01-19"
  },
  {
    "question": "1 point for each flag showing a weapon of an armor. [Angola - Machete, Barbados - Trident, Belize - Two Clubs/Two axes, Guatemala - Two guns w/Bayonet, Kenya - Two Spears and a shield, Mozambique - AK47 Rifle, Saudi Arabia - Sabre, Sri Lanka - Dagger held by Griffon, Swaziland - Two spears and shield, US Virgin Islands - 3 arrows]",
    "answer": "14",
    "tags": "general knowledge",
    "date": "2024-01-19"
  },
  {
    "question": "In which city is located the European Central Bank?",
    "answer": "Frankfurt",
    "tags": "general knowledge",
    "date": "2024-01-19"
  },
  {
    "question": "The queen of which Country recently abdicated?",
    "answer": "Denmark",
    "tags": "general knowledge",
    "date": "2024-01-19"
  },
  {
    "question": "The 2024 edition of the most famous Rally in the world has recently started in Saudi Arabia. What's the name of the event?",
    "answer": "Rally Dakar",
    "tags": "sport",
    "date": "2024-01-19"
  },
  {
    "question": "2024 will be the year of the olympiads. In which month will they start?",
    "answer": "July 26th",
    "tags": "sport",
    "date": "2024-01-19"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which athlete recently announced the termination of his contract with Nike?",
    "answer": "Tiger Woods",
    "tags": "sport",
    "date": "2024-01-19"
  },
  {
    "question": "Luke Litt became recently famous for finishing at the age of 16 in the final round of which sport?",
    "answer": "Darts",
    "tags": "sport",
    "date": "2024-01-19"
  },
  {
    "question": "There's currently undergoing the \"Tour Down Under\", a famous January cycling competition. Where is this competition held?",
    "answer": "Australia",
    "tags": "sport",
    "date": "2024-01-19"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who was elected the FIFA coach of the year?",
    "answer": "Pep Guardiola",
    "tags": "sport",
    "date": "2024-01-19"
  },
  {
    "question": "In 2024, the TV series Happy Days will be 50 years old. How's called the family to which Ron Howard belongs?",
    "answer": "Cunningham",
    "tags": "TV",
    "date": "2024-01-19"
  },
  {
    "question": "Jenna Fischer and Angela Kinsey, better known as Pam and Angela, are the hosts of which famous \"the Office\" podcast?",
    "answer": "Office ladies",
    "tags": "TV",
    "date": "2024-01-19"
  },
  {
    "question": "Whych reference book published in 1858, often considered the \"doctor's bible\", gave it's name to a famous TV Series?",
    "answer": "Grey's Anatomy",
    "tags": "TV",
    "date": "2024-01-19"
  },
  {
    "question": "The script of which famous TV series was recently found in a trashbin and sold at an auction for more than 24k dollars?",
    "answer": "Friends",
    "tags": "TV",
    "date": "2024-01-19"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which was the most watched Netflix show in 2023, by number of hours watched?",
    "answer": "The Night Agent, more than 800 million hours",
    "tags": "TV",
    "date": "2024-01-19"
  },
  {
    "question": "In the TV series \"Suits\", Louis Litt keeps in his office the ashes of whom?",
    "answer": "Norma, the former secretary",
    "tags": "TV",
    "date": "2024-01-19"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which celerity recently entered in the restricted group of the so called EGOT?",
    "answer": "Elton John won in 2024 the Emmy, together with Emmy, Grammy, Oscar and Tony award",
    "tags": "movies",
    "date": "2024-01-19"
  },
  {
    "question": "2024 will be the year of the last season of \"The Crown\". Which character said \"I found women in general tend not to be suited for this role\" because they get too emotional?",
    "answer": "Margaret Thatcher",
    "tags": "TV",
    "date": "2024-01-19"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which famous school of art, drama and music was the origin host of more than 100 Emmys, 24 academy awards and 12 Pulitzer Prizes?",
    "answer": "Juilliard School",
    "tags": "movies",
    "date": "2024-01-19"
  },
  {
    "question": "In the 2024 Golden Globes, who won the most prizes on each movie and TV category?",
    "answer": "Oppenheimer-movie, Succession-tv",
    "tags": "movies",
    "date": "2024-01-19"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is the zip code of Beverly Hills?",
    "answer": "90210",
    "tags": "TV",
    "date": "2024-01-19"
  }
]
